<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Relentless Optimizer</title>
    <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Relentless Optimizer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Travel Loadout in a 12L Daypack</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2025/10/07/travel-loadout-in-a-12l-daypack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2025/10/07/travel-loadout-in-a-12l-daypack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love traveling light and the one bag concept, but had never actually fit everything into a single bag. I’m picky about certain items - I want my iPad setup, ice water in a vacuum bottle, and my Sonicare toothbrush. On past trips, I learned I also needed a good daypack - two comfortable straps, back ventilation, and some internal structure. I didn’t think a daypack would fit in another bag, so I figured I was stuck with a rolling suitcase plus daypack. Then, on my last trip, I got some great quick-drying clothes and tried out “hotel sink laundry”, and found that it worked! Everything was dry by morning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M4 iPad Pro 11 Charging</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2024/10/08/m4-ipad-pro-11-charging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2024/10/08/m4-ipad-pro-11-charging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently bought an M4 iPad Pro 11&amp;quot; and couldn&amp;rsquo;t find detailed charging data about it. Here are my measurements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID Road Trip: An Unexpected Journey</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/07/21/covid-road-trip-an-unexpected-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/07/21/covid-road-trip-an-unexpected-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After two years of minimal travel, we decided to fly to New York City, and I promptly got COVID while there. Our return turned into a surprise COVID road trip; this is the story.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search for the Ultimate Indoor Sweater</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/06/01/search-for-the-ultimate-indoor-sweater/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/06/01/search-for-the-ultimate-indoor-sweater/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For most of my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve bought clothes on sale which seemed &amp;ldquo;good enough&amp;rdquo;. My outerwear lasts a really long time, though. As a few favorites finally wore out, I decided that I should really just get exactly what I want and get rid of the rest. With that, my quest for some perfect sweaters began.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M1 MacBooks charge from anything!</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/05/04/m1-macbooks-charge-from-anything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2022/05/04/m1-macbooks-charge-from-anything/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently started using an M1 MacBook Pro 14&amp;quot;. I wanted to know which of my cables and chargers work with it and how fast it charges from them. My previous laptop, an ASUS Zephyrus G14, only charges from 20v (60w+) USB-C chargers, so I was expecting the same. I was shocked to find out that the MacBook will charge from &lt;strong&gt;every charger I have&lt;/strong&gt;, at any voltage!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Galaxy Watch 4 Battery Life</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2021/10/11/samsung-galaxy-watch-4-battery-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2021/10/11/samsung-galaxy-watch-4-battery-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My Samsung Galaxy Watch 4 battery ran out on the first day by 4:00pm, and I was pretty disappointed. After a few device resets and a lot of measurements, however, my watch is now using only about a third of the battery per full 24 hour day. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I learned.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Phone Experiment: Taking Back My Attention</title>
      <link>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2021/09/24/no-phone-experiment-taking-back-my-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://relentlessoptimizer.com/life/2021/09/24/no-phone-experiment-taking-back-my-attention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Samsung Galaxy Watch 4 recently came out, and it inspired me to try going phone-free, carrying only the watch. I spend too much time glued to my phone, and I wanted to take back my attention, but I know I need to be reachable. For me, the core problem is the endless scrolling apps - Reddit, YouTube, Google News, and a few pages-of-links websites I obsessively visit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
